Himanshu Jaichand Bharti

Full stack developer

Oubai +971 557556434

Summary

Dedicated, self motivated and enthusiastic full stack developer. Experienced in evaluating and improving existing websites and applications to enhance user experience and functionality. Proven success in planning and implementing complex technical solutions to detailed client briefs and requirements. Hardworking team player with problem-solving, ideas-sharing approach to full stack development.

Experience

Voeux Information Technology

Oct 2023 - Present

Full stack developer

- https://metavoeux.io/
- Developed the **web3** application using **reactjs**, **etherjs**, **nodejs** and **solidity**. Where users can create their **NFTs** and sell them.
- Did the testing and Integration of smart contracts.
- Wrote the smart contract for the distribution of user rewards, using which user can claim their rewards based on the points they have accumulated.

Red. Health

April 2021 - December 2022

Full stack developer

Hyderabad

- https://www.red.health/
- 1. Upgraded the CRM from **angular 7 to angular 13**. This helped us integration of calling SDK in our CRM.
- 2. Built a page for **hospital onboarding** in our business application. Earlier onboarding was done manually by our team.
- 3. Engineered a **React Native app** for the driver side, reducing ambulance arrival time from 15 minutes to 5 minutes.
- 4. Conducted app deployments on Google Cloud Platform (GCP).

Education

Inidian Institute Of Information Technology Guwahati

July 2016 - May 2020

• • • 0 0

Regular

6.89

. . . .

https://www.iiitg.ac.in/

Computer Science and Engineering

Projects

Image Captcha application

An intuitive application that retrieves images, prompting users to identify and click on two similar images for an engaging and interactive experience.

Random Image Sharing App

Its a simple app which fetches random images and prompts social media buttons for sharing

Skills	Javascript	Node js	React	Angular	
	• • • • •	• • • • 0	• • • • 0	• • • • 0	
	React Native	GCP, AWS	React Native	CSS	
	• • • 0 0	• • • • •	\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$	
	HTML	MongoDB	Postgress	Git	
	• • • • ○ Nest js • • • • ○	• • • • 0	• • • • •	• • • • 0	
		Typescript			
		• • • • 0			
Languages	Hindi	English I		arathi	

. . . . 0